Hello.
こんにちは
Your posture is really good.
めっちゃ姿勢がいいですね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Is that better?
そっちがいいのかな?
on second thoughts.
やっぱり
Well, you look quite young,
えっと、だいぶ若く見えるんですけど、
Is that so? You're not a high school student or anything, are you?
あれですか、高校生とかじゃないですよね?
It's not.
じゃないです
How old are you now?
今、おいくつですか?
I'm currently a university student and I'm 21 years old.
今は大学生で21歳です
university student?
大学生?
I wonder what type it is?
何系だろうな?
a,
あ、
So, can I take a guess?
じゃあ ちょっと当ててみていいですか?
It seems like she's really good at motherhood,
ちょっとあの、母性よくすぐらいそうなんで、
As a nurse.
看護師で
No.
違います
different?
違う?
yes.
はい
Eh, then what type is it?
え、じゃあ何系ですか?
Well, I'm a pastry chef who makes sweets.
えっと、お菓子作ったりするパティシエの
So, what if you're a chef and you're a pastry chef?
じゃあ、調理師系のやつでパティシエを先行していれば?
yes.
はい
Do you like sweets like that?
そんなお菓子好きなの?
Well, I've been making it for a long time.
そうですね、昔から結構作ってます
Actually, I also really like sweets.
もう、実は俺もめちゃくちゃお菓子好きなんですよ
Well, I'm an eater.
まあ、僕食べる方なんですけど
Well, you can tell by looking at this body type.
まあ、この体型見ればわかりますよね
What do you think?
なんだと思う?
I'm starting to like that kind of thing.
ああいうの好きそうになってます
No, really.
いや、もう本当に
Well, that's nice, I'll make you some sweets.
えー、いいですね、なんかお菓子作ってくれる
pretty girl.
かわいい女の子
That's nice.
いいなぁ
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Actually, I have very pale skin.
という か、めっちゃ肌白いんですけど、
Well, I wonder where you're from.
えーっと、まあ、出身はどこだろうなぁ
Then, in Akita.
じゃあ、秋田で
It's a shame.
惜しい
Is it a shame?
惜しい?
Ah, what a shame?
あ、惜しい?
So, where is it?
じゃあ、どこですか?
This is Miyagi.
宮城です
Oh, Miyagi?
あ、宮城?
yes.
はい
When you say Miyagi, do you think there is a place like that or Sendai?
宮城って言うと、あれか、仙台とかあると思う?
That's right, that's right.
そうです、そうです
I go there often too.
僕もよく行きますよ
Are you going?
行きますか
I'm going.
行きます
Well then, maybe we can meet.
じゃあ、会っとるかもしれないですね
Are you meeting?
会っとるですか
I often go there to eat Zunda shakes.
ずんだシェイクを食べによく行くんですよ
Ah, that's delicious, Zunda Shake.
あー、おいしいですね、ずんだシェイク
It's delicious there.
あ そこ、あそこおいしいですよ
We've only been talking about food since a while ago.
さっきから食い物の話しかしないんだよね
That's right.
ですね
It's true.
ほんとだね
If we keep going like this, we'll be talking about food for an hour.
このままだったら食い物の話1時間話しちゃうから
Well, a little.
まあ、ちょっとね
Well, you have amazing legs, they're beautiful.
まあ、すごい足がね、きれいだから、
I've been looking at you all the time.
ずっとそっちを見てるんだけど
By the way, I'm currently 21 years old and a college student.
ちなみに、今21歳、大学生
yes.
はい
What about your boyfriend?
彼氏は?
I don't have a boyfriend right now.
彼氏は今いないです
He's not there right now.
今いないんだ
So, have you ever said that you're not there?
じゃあ、今いないってことは今までは言った?
I agree.
そうですね
Yes, there are 3 people with experience.
経験は3人あって、はい
Well then, I have three boyfriends as well.
じゃあ、彼氏も3人だ
The two of us are boyfriends, but wait a minute.
2人は彼氏なんですけど、 ちょっとまて
Wait a minute.
ちょっとまって
Yes, the two of them are boyfriends, but the two of them are boyfriends.
はい、2人は彼氏なんですけど、 2人は彼氏って、
Where did the third one come from?
3人目はどこから出てきたの?
One of them had a little one-night stand with a senior.
1人は先輩とちょっとワンナイトしてた
Isn't it time to get married?
それは結婚の時じゃないの?
University?
大学?
That's right, university.
そうです、大学です
Did you have a one-night stand with a senior from your university?
大学の先輩とワンナイトしてた?
How about that?
それはどうだろう?
May I ask?
聞いていいのかな?
Not because he was confessed to, but just by force?
告白されてとかじゃなくて、普通に勢いで?
Or something...
それともなんか...
I agree.
そうですね
There's a drinking party, a drinking party?
飲み会があって、 飲 み会?
There was a welcome party or something like that in the new building.
歓迎会みたいなのがあって、 新館?
Then, I realized that I was living alone.
それで、気づいたら、一人暮らししてるんですけど、
What a kettle of fish.
なんやかんやで
I came to Tokyo, went to the new building, was made to drink,
上京してきて、新館行って、飲まされて、
Rather than taking it home, I think you were forced into it.
お 持ち帰りしたというよりは、押しかけられたと?
Well, it's like that.
まあ、そんな感じ
Were you sent away?
送り狼をされたんですか?
I agree.
そうですね
I worked with that senior, and with that senior,
その先輩でやっちゃって、その先輩とは、
How do you feel now?
今はどんな感じなんですか?
Don't you know if we're dating?
付き合ったりとか知らないですか?
We're not dating right now though.
今は、付き合ってはないですけど
So you're not that good at sex?
そんなにエッチが上手くなかったと?
That's not the case.
そんなことないです
That's suspicious.
怪しいな
That's not the case.
そんなことないです
Maybe he was too drunk to stand up?
たぶん、酔っ払ってたから立たなかったのかな?
Poor me.
かわいそうに
If there were 3 people with experience in sex,
エッチの身に経験人数3人だったら、
Well, if there were three of us, we might not know yet,
まあ、3人だったらまだわかんないかもしれないですけど、
Do you like sex?
セックスは好きですか?
I don't hate it.
嫌いじゃないです
That's a good answer.
いい答えです
If I didn't hate it, if I didn't, I wouldn't have come here.
嫌いじゃなかったらね、 嫌いだったらここに来ないもんね
Why did you come here?
なんで、ここに来ちゃったのかな?
Really.
本当に
Why?
なんでですかね
Well, I'm glad I got to meet such a cute girl.
まあ、私はね、こんなかわいい子に会えたからいいですけどね
By the way, there were 3 people with experience, and one of them was an okurigokami.
ちなみに、経験人数3人で、1人は送りごかみだったんですけど、
Have you ever played anything unusual with your two boyfriends?
彼氏2人と変わったプレイとかしたことありますか?
A strange play.
変わったプレイ
At school, at the gymnasium, outside, etc.
学校でとか、体育倉庫でとか、外でとか
But what about the toilet?
でも、トイレとか?
toilet!?
トイレ!?
Seriously?
まじで?
When I was in high school, I wondered if there was a toilet in high school.
高校生の時に、確かに高校生でトイレもあるか、
Hotels are expensive too.
ホテルもね、お金かかるもんね
I agree.
そうですね
Is it the men's or women's restroom?
それは、男子トイレ、女子トイレ?
That's the women's toilet.
それは、女子トイレ
Women's toilet!?
女子トイレ!?
Boyfriend, you're awesome!
彼氏、やばいね!
This is terrible.
やばいです
Is it a park or a commercial facility?
それは、公園とか、それとも商業施設とか?
It's a park.
公園です
I was surprised when I heard that it was a commercial facility.
びっくり、商業施設って言ったら、
The security guard will get mad at you, really.
警備員に怒られるよ、本当に
I'll take you home.
連れて帰っちゃう
Yes, really.
ね、本当にね
You can take me home and I'll pass you around.
連れて帰れて、回されちゃうよね
Where is the color manga?
どこが色漫画だって
It doesn't look like it, but it's naughty.
見かけに言わらず、エッチなんですね
What kind of play do you like?
どういうプレーが好きですか?
What kind of play?
どういうプレー?
Ordinary play or flirting.
普通のプレーとか、イチャイチャとか
Well, I had a lot of fun today.
まあ、今日は存分にイチャイチャしちゃった
Where is the erogenous body?
性感体どこですか?
The erogenous body is the chest.
性感体は、胸
chest?
胸?
Hands to the side.
手を横に
Hold your chest up.
胸張って
Is it big?
大きいですか?
How many cups?
何カップ?
this.
これ
A cup?
Aカップ?
It's D.
Dです
Is it D?
Dなの?
This just checks my nerves.
ちょっとこれは神経を確かめる
This is by no means an erotic voice,
これは決してエロい声ではありませんからね、
Really.
本当に
I wonder if the picture below was underwear?
これの下図、下着だったのかな?
I thought he was wearing something, but...
何か、色々着てるもんだと思ってたけど、
It was underwear.
下着だったのね
You're not wearing anything.
何も着てないね
By any chance, did you wear this today?
まさか、これで着たの、今日?
Isn't it dangerous?
やばくない?
So, let's summarize a little.
じゃあ、ちょっとまとめましょうね
Mr. Czech, I got this.
チェコさん、これ持ったんだけどさ、
Is your bra size too small?
ブラのサイズ小さくない?
When did you buy this bra?
これいつ買ったブラ?
This was a while ago.
これちょっと前です
You bought this before you went to university, definitely.
大学入る前に買ったでしょ、これ絶対に
I think it's gotten a little bigger.
ちょっとね、大きくなっちゃったのかなって
I was really disappointed in the second one.
第二に揉まれたの、本当に
Oh, lie, lady is huge.
え、嘘、レディーなんて、でかい
perhaps.
多分
Sounds nice, sort of.
いい音ですね、ちょっとね
This is nice and soft.
いい柔らかさだね、これね
Well, well, well, well, right?
まあまあ、まあまあ、でしょ
No, I have to wear a bra that hugs my body.
だめよ、体に当たるブラしないと
Hey, these are really nice breasts.
ちょっとこれはね、これはすごい良いおっぱいですね
This is good.
これは良いものだもん
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
It's amazing, it's amazing to see the reaction around here.
すっごい、すっごいここら辺に散ると反応いいね
It's easy, isn't it?
めんせい簡単なんだ、そういうのね
I kind of forgot how beautiful her breasts were.
胸の綺麗さに忘れてたわ、ちょっと
Please wait a moment.
ちょっと待ってもらって
Excuse me.
失礼します
Ah, I clicked this based on the imagination of many people.
あ、なんか大勢の想像でこれ押したの
Isn't it really stylish?
めっちゃスタイル良くない?
is that so?
そうですか?
Yeah, great style.
うん、すっげースタイル良い
So cute.
かわいいな
But, the pants are even higher than what I received.
でもね、貰った以上にパンツがハイエグだって
That's erotic
エロいな、
this.
これ
I was a little impressed, a little.
ちょっと 感心しちゃったもん、ちょっと
Try pointing your butt this way.
こっちにお尻向けてみて
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
はい、はい、はい、はい
Well, she has a really nice butt,
え、めちゃくちゃ良いお尻なんですけど、
This is a little bit.
これちょっと
Fair-skinned.
色白な
Okay.
よ いしょ
Ah, this is necessary, so just a moment.
あ、これ必要なことなんで、ちょっと
It's necessary, so I touch the front mirror for a moment.
必要なことなんで、ちょっとね、前鏡に手ついて
Stick your butt out.
お尻突き出して
Get your hands on it.
手つける
This is a nice ass.
これは良いお尻だな
She has a really beautiful butt.
めっちゃ綺麗なお尻してる
Oh no.
やば
Oh, sorry, I'm just a little intrigued.
あ、ごめんごめん、ちょっとね、興味をそそられちゃった
Wow, what a nice butt.
え、めっちゃ良いお尻
She has always had a beautiful body.
ずっと綺麗な体してる
sorry.
すみません
Just a little bit.
ちょっとね
Yeah.
うん
What is it?
なんですか?
Please check, please tell me how to check.
チェックをね、チェックを教えてください
check.
チェック
Check, check.
チ ェ ック、チェックね
check.
チェック
That's a good lie.
良い横するね
She has a really, really beautiful butt.
めちゃくちゃ、本当に綺麗なお尻してる
Oh, Peta.
あ、ペタ
Don't upload 3.
3個アップしないで
Suddenly, I'm brushing without saying a word.
いきなり無言でブラシをしてる
We had talked many times before, and we had the same opinion.
さっきも何度も喋ってて、同じ意見で喋ってた
Surprised.
びっくり
I became obsessed with removing the brush.
ブラシは外すのに夢中になっちゃった
It's beautiful.
綺麗なね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
It's seriously erotic.
マジでエロいな
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Excuse me.
失礼します
It's heavy.
重 たい
Excuse me.
失礼します
scared.
怖い
a,
あ、
It still feels good.
や っぱりいい感じ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいの?
I see.
そっか
Such a beautiful chikubi.
こんな綺麗なチクビして
That's erotic.
エロいな
You really like erotic things, right?
本当はエロいこと好きでしょ?
Really?
本当に?
It's really good.
本当にいいよ
Can I hang out with you for an hour?
ちょっと1時間もんでていい?
No?
ダメ?
It's going to get bigger.
大きくなっちゃう
Make this big.
大きくするんだ、これ
So cute.
かわいいな
ERROR
すえろ
It's a little erotic.
ちょっとエロいな
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Makes you look embarrassed.
恥ずかしいぽくさせる
cute.
かわいい
That's a beautiful shaved pussy.
綺麗なパイパンですね
It's not really wet.
めっちゃ濡れてない
No.
ダメ
I don't get angry.
怒らない
No.
ダメ
Step back a little.
ちょっと後ろに寄って
Put your feet here.
足をね、こっちに置いて
You can take your hand out from below.
手をね、下から出せるから
Let's expand it.
広げてみよう
You have a really beautiful body.
本当に綺麗な体してるね
No way.
やだ
It's a little wet.
ちょっと 濡れてますね
difficult.
難しい
Are you okay.
大丈夫
My uncle is also embarrassed.
おじさんも恥ずかしい
Chestnuts are really big.
栗めっちゃ大きい
Chestnuts are big.
栗大きいね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I wonder if it's easy on my fingers.
指 に甘えちゃうかな
It's a shame that I've spoiled you.
恥 ず かしいの甘えさしちゃって
It's embarrassing that I'm spoiled.
恥ずかしいの甘えさしちゃって
sorry.
ご めん
My penis is a little
おちんちんがちょっと、
Hello.
こんにちは
Hello, I did it.
こんにちは しちゃったんだけど
penis.
おちんちん
You feel disgusting.
お前、気持ち悪いな
Blow out as much wind as you can with the spatula.
ヘラが置いてるだけ風を吹き出して
I'm relieved.
おしんつきだしな
You must be nervous.
緊張するでしょ
Get your hands on it.
手ついて
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Because I can't do that.
そんなものできないから